The experiments we've run so far
prove that the D-mails are being sent to the past.
But I couldn't change the outcome of my match with Feyris-tan!
That's a problem with you, not with the D-mail.
There are problems with the system,
including the issue with Rukako,
but if we work on it, we can turn it into a real time machine...
Time machine?
You were listening to us?
Feyris just brought your order!
Do you want any gum syrup or milk?
I refuse!
And thus, you can have my everything!
There it is!
Secret Move: Stir While Gazing Into Their Eyes!
I'm so jealous, Okarin. Explode.
Kyouma, what do you mean by a time machine?
Do you think you can seduce me
into giving up classified information?
I won't ask Kyouma.
Daru-nyan!
You think Daru would betray me?
We built a machine that sends texts to the past!
And by "we," I mean mostly me!
That was entirely too fast!
Messages to the past?
Even the number of several billion heartbeats
suujuuoku mo no kodou no kazu sae
anata ni wa matataki teido no saji na toukyuu
is basic research with little glamor for you
kako ni torawarete mirai wo nageku mo
Even locked in the past and lamenting the future
chiri hitotsu gosan wo yurusanu hitsuzen
it's an inevitability that won't forgive miscalculating one speck of dust
mugen ni hirogaru yume mo egaku mirai mo
The dreams that stretch out forever and the future we imagine
bokutachi ni yurusareta kyoei no genri
are a vain theory we allowed
yuugen sore wa futatsu no hari ga shimesu
Finity, that's what the two hands of the clock point out
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
towards a cruel agreement and choice
Hacking to the Gate
zankoku na yakujou to sentaku e hacking to the gate
dakara ima ichibyou goto ni sekaisen wo koete
That's why I want to cross world lines with each passing second
kimi no sono egao mamoritai no sa
and protect your smile
soshite mata kanashimi no nai jikan no loop e to
And once again, into a time loop that contains no sadness
nomikomareteyuku kodoku no kansokusha
A swallowed solitary observer
Chaos Theory
Homeostasis
Stupid Daru...
Spreading our secrets to outsiders...
Why?
Why must you take it that way?
I just wanted to...
No, that isn't what I meant!
I...
Wh-Wh-What?
I'm not crying!
It's not like I was crying, okay?
You were clearly crying...
Your eyes are still red.
No!
Something's in my eye...
What is this, an old soap opera?
Anyway, I'm not crying.
So no questions.
Got it?
I didn't say anything.
Shut up!
Christina...
Don't talk to me!
I'll only say this...
You're part of my life now.
Any time you want to talk, I'll listen.
Okabe...
Just as planned, she fell for it!
Now I can use her for all the grunt work!
Hey.
Good work out there!
Feyris-chan!
Are you heading to Kyouma's?
Yeah, he wanted me to bring lunch.
Hey, have you seen the time machine, Mayushii?
Time...
Oh, Phone Microwave-san?
Phone Microwave?
There's this big spooky lightning, and it's kind of scary...
Wow!
It's like a time machine out of the movies.
Yeah...
But Mayushii doesn't really want him doing that stuff.
Why?
It feels like Okarin is leaving me.
We will now begin our Round—
Okarin! Okarin!
What?
Isn't this strange?
Mayushii says she isn't cosplaying.
It isn't cosplay.
It's her school uniform.
I had school today.
It's a super-realistic portrayal of a school uniform.
That's sexual harassment, and she doesn't have to accept it.
Here's yours, Okarin!
Thanks.
No, wait. I said we're having a Round Table!
You're the one who wanted me to bring lunch.
Don't mind him.
Obviously, it isn't anything important.
You can say that after you hear the discussion topic...
Physical time travel!
Mayuri, is there still barley tea in the fridge?
One second.
Realistic.
It's me!
The Organization has initiated an operation to tear apart the lab.
The words of me, Hououin Kyouma,
fail to reach them!
Do they ever?
Then why are you ignoring my awesome topic?
Because it's impossible.
We can send messages to the past.
It must be possible...
It's not.
We can send thirty-six bytes plus some extra.
Three messages, with six characters.
No more.
If you want to experiment, why not be the guinea pig?
That's if you don't mind ending up as a gel-Okarin.
Gel-Okarin, huh?
That'd really hurt.
SERN's experiments prove the difficulties
inherent to physical time travel.
Even using the LHC, biggest in the world,
they've had no success.
We can't possibly do it with this equipment.
Then how do the messages get to the past?
I don't know.
That's the problem.
Like I said before,
SERN's trying to use the lifter-black hole combination
to achieve time travel.
The Phone Microwave probably works on the same principle.
But the microwave doesn't have anything
to function as a lifter.
So where is it?
I don't know.
We're limited in the times we can send D-mail, too.
Currently, we can't be sure that this machine
really sends messages to the past.
Before we continue,
we should deal with the issues before us first.
Boring!
99.9% of science is boring.
If you call yourself a scientist...
I'm not a scientist!
I'm a mad scientist!
Yo, I heard you like fail, so we put some fail in your fail,
so you can facepalm while you facepalm.
Miss Makise...
You aren't a...
Shut up!
Not another word!
Because that's impossible!
Get back on topic, already.
Continuing on to the reports.
How's the translation of
the SERN server documents going, Christina?
AKA, 2channer!
I told you that's not true!
Then you sure know your memes.
I do not!
Nothing to report.
I see.
Continue your investigations...
2channer!
Stop calling me that!
Daru's up next. How's the hacking coming?
No change.
Probably, until I analyze the mysterious program
on the other server, there'll be no change.
How's the IBN 5100 analysis going?
Be great if I could do it.
What do you mean?
Huh?
You haven't started the analysis?
How should I do that?
Where's the IBN 5100?
How would I know?
It can't be...
Okarin, what's wrong?
Christina...
Did I, by any chance, not find the IBN 5100?
You don't even know where it is.
I see.
So if I decide to believe what you say, you found the IBN 5100.
Yes.
I carried it back here with you.
But you're the only one with any memory of that.
The D-mails probably changed the past.
Changed the past...
But we've only sent minor stuff.
The Butterfly Effect.
Sending one message into the past
causes the world line to split.
From a world where we didn't buy a Lotto-6 ticket
to one where we did.
Little by little, this changes what was meant to happen.
One change causes another,
and they pile on top of one another.
It's one of the long-recognized risks of altering the past.
Then where is the IBN 5100?
Let me ask this instead.
Where was it?
Yes, when I asked my dad, he said it used to be here, but...
It's gone now.
I see.
Well?
There was an IBN 5100 at Yanabayashi Shrine.
But it's gone now.
No one knows when it was taken or by whom.
A dead end, huh?
But it's strange to donate a PC to a shrine.
I wonder who'd have done that.
Feyris-chan?
What's up?
Here's the list I wrote of ten questions
to ask the maids, at the next event.
Let me see...
"If you could go back and redo one thing from your past, what would it be?"
What would you do, Feyris-chan?
Let me think...
Feyris... doesn't look back at her past! Let's go.
It's the task of the cat-eared maid,
who brings everyone happiness, to forge ahead!
Oh, my phone!
Hi, this is Feyris.
Kyouma.
A PC?
An IBN 5100.
Did your family give it to Yanabayashi Shrine?
I don't really remember...
But you're right. My dad did have a lot of old PCs.
Kyouma...
Is this related to the time machine
you were talking about?
Look, look!
It's an Upa!
A metal Upa!
Do you still want a metal Upa?
Still?
How long are you going to stand there, staring at it?
Wait!
Daru-kun!
Here I am!
What are you buying?
I found a limited-edition that had sold out before I could buy it!
You might say,
"This encounter was the choice of Steins Gate!"
Don't use it for stuff like this!
Anyway, why are you two following me?
You could've stayed back at the lab, with the assistant.
Once I heard you were going to Feyris-tan's place,
I had to come along!
I wanted to go and play, too!
Why did Feyris tell me to come to her house?
It's Kirari-chan!
Mayuri, wait...
Jeez...
The IBN 5100.
Shining Finger!
Wait! Hey!
Shining...
Moeka!
Kiryuu Moeka!
Why?
FB said it was there!
Okabe-kun...
Back there, you mentioned the IBN 5100...
Do you know... where it is?
You don't know, either?
I don't...
Okarin!
Moeka-san?
Yeah.
Okabe...
Moeka-san's so pretty and stylish.
I'm sure she'd make a great cosplayer.
Mayuri, you know Shining Finger?
I do!
How?
How do you know her?
You brought her to the lab!
After Moeka sent her D-mail,
she disappeared from everyone's memory.
And then, after Ruka sent his D-mail,
they knew her again.
Little by little, the world changes,
each time the D-mail changes the past?
Is this really the place?
I'm sure of it.
Seems it's on the top floor.
The mistress will be here soon.
Just one moment.
Butler cafés aren't my thing.
A real butler!
I've never seen one before.
Look!
The people all look like ants!
I love it!
Okarin...
Thought he'd say that!
Sorry for the wait.
Feyris-chan!
Now it's Feyris-tan wearing her normal clothes!
What luck!
Feyris Nyan Nyan!
It seems I must question your true identity!
Feyris is...
...Feyris-nyan!
Stop fooling around!
If you refuse to explain, then I'm leaving!
Oh, fine.
Feyris's family owns all the land around here!
Then Akiba is...
That's right.
What about Akiba now?
It's Feyris's real name.
Akiha Rumiho-chan!
I didn't hear that!
Feyris-tan's real name is Feyris-tan!
A sad attempt to escape reality.
By the way, Feyris was the one
who asked to bring moe culture to Akiba.
No way!
And she works as an angel at May Queen,
to further spread moe culture!
How splendid!
And my eyes are also splendid,
for recognizing her before anyone else!
But, but... Keep it a secret, okay?
I want you to treat me
with Feyris-love, just like always!
I will! Totally!
Thank you, nyan-nyan!
No nyan-nyan!
Anyway, what about the IBN 5100?
Oh, that?
But before that, I have a simple request...
You want to arrange a trade?
It's nothing difficult.
I only want you to let me use the D-mail. Just once.
Sure!
Use it as often as you want!
Wait! The D-mail is absolutely off-limits to outsiders...
Then why not make Feyris-chan a lab member, too?
Wait! Wait!
Sending more messages to the past would be—
You're the one who sent the Lotto-6 number back,
to try and make money!
And you can't send one for Feyris-tan?
Just once!
No, that's not it...
But if I stop now,
there's no guarantee that the IBN 5100 will return.
If this becomes any kind of clue...
Very well.
But just as Mayuri said,
you'll have to become a lab member.
You are now Lab Member 007, Akiha Ru—
I-I-I can't hear you!
It's done.
You're sure you want to send it back ten years, right?
I'm sure!
What does it say?
Well... It's a secret!
Tell me.
As leader of the lab, I have a duty to know.
No. A maiden's private life is off-limits to guys.
I think it's wrong to look at someone's mail.
I agree! Totally!
Fine.
Then put your hand on the send button and wait.
Hello?
It's me!
What's the situation...
She hung up on me, damn it!
Yeah, I bet she did.
That Christina!
Doesn't she know she's my assistant?
Hello?
It's Hououin Kyouma. Don't just disconnect me, without a word.
Hououin? Oh, Okabe.
I thought it was a prank call.
You saw my number on the display.
Even so, those first words
are creepy enough to make me hang up.
In other words, you are terrified of the mighty Hououin Kyouma—
She hung up on me! She hung up on me again!
Okarin, aren't you ready yet?
Wait!
Curse you, cold-blooded, pervert girl genius...
Hello?
Listen, The Zomb—
Hello, my name is Okabe Rintarou.
What is it?
I would be extraordinarily gratified
if you'd set the Phone Microwave (name subject to change)
to the values I proferred in my earlier message.
You should have just said that from the start.
Also, that isn't what "proffer" means.
You're embarrassing yourself.
And stop calling it the Phone Microwave
(name subject to change), already.
Shut up, Cel-7!
I'm trying to be polite, and you're...
Do they not like each other?
I think it's the opposite.
Agreed.
Will you send?
Maybe...
Maybe I don't need to do this.
Feyris!
The electricity's started.
Send it.
Um...
Who are you?
Daddy!
Daddy?
Were you talking to Kyouma?
Yeah.
I'll be on my way.
Enjoy yourselves.
Feyris-chan's dad has this
kind of refined air about him, doesn't he?
Indeed! You can tell he's Feyris-tan's dad.
Um...
Do you know anything about an IBN 5100?
I haven't heard that name in ages.
I'm looking for one.
Unfortunately, I parted with mine a long time ago.
Did you give it to Yanabayashi Shrine?
Shrine?
No, I didn't.
Goodbye, then.
Before Feyris sent her D-mail,
I heard that the IBN 5100 disappeared after it had been given to Yanabayashi Shrine.
But now, the shrine never got it.
Each time we send a message, things change.
Something may be changing,
even without my being aware of it.
It's possible that we've already done something that can't be undone.
kisei sareta chikai mujihi naru, juuni no shinri nogarerarenai
We cannot escape the 12 merciless truths and the controlled oath we took
Okarin! Okarin!
Mayushii is going to Nakano to buy an Ai-Sword doujinshi.
Ai-Sword?
Kouga Yui?
Nakano's far away.
Yeah.
I wish there were a Tora no Ana here.
ansoku no asu wo negattara
If we wish for a tomorrow full of rest
What are you talking about?
Tora no Ana's right over there.
te no naka no toutoi jishou no chihei he
to be given to the precious event horizon in our hands
What are you talking about, Okarin?
Why would there be one in Akiba?
toraware shi meiyaku arawareta gishou no rinkaku
In the promise we made in captivity appeared the contours of a lie
seimei no tenchi wa moumoku na jikan wo kizanda
The realm of life recorded a time of blindness
habatake butterfly
Fly, butterfly
kiseki no butterfly
O, miraculous butterfly
anata he sasagu
I will sacrifice to you
namida no butterfly
Butterflies of tears
mabushii butterfly
Dazzling butterflies
subete ga ima kakikaerareru
Everything is being rewritten